https://www.merrickmint.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Categories
** 2021 Year of the OX **
Famous Golden Holograms BillsPolychromatic BillsFamous DUAL 8's Set24KT Gold BillsOriginal Zodiac BillsRed Blast Polychrome Zodiac BillsCoinsLimited EditionsLunar Red Hologram BillsLarge Size BillsLucky Money Federal Reserve Banknotes (Red Folders)Other Lucky Money Themed BillsCNY Envelopes
Colorized Coins
JFK Kennedy Half DollarsArtAstrology/HoroscopesAnimalsEntertainmentGifts & OccasionsHistoric PlacesHoliday & SeasonalMilitariaMisc JFK Half DollarsPoliticalScience & NatureSportsTransportationWeaponsWild WestWorld/Historical EventsStatehood QuartersEntertainmentHistoric PlacesMilitariaMisc Statehood QuartersPoliticalSportsWorld/Historical EventsWorld Trade Center 9/11Presidential $1 DollarsSacagawea DollarsEisenhower IKE DollarAmerican Silver EagleAmerica the Beautiful Parks QuartersMisc Colorized Coins
Hologram Coins
U.S. Statehood QuartersMisc Hologram Coins
24K Gold Plated Coins
Sports
Football (NFL)BaseballHockey (NHL)Nascar
Entertainment
Commemorative Coins
Colorized Currency
EntertainmentEnhanced Bills (all denominations)SportsPolitical$2 Parks/States$2 Statehood$1 StatesWorld/Historical EventsMisc Bills
Hologram Currency
Presidential $1 Coins
Colorized24K Gold Plated
Misc Presidential $1
America the Beautiful Parks Quarters
Colorized24K Gold PlatedHologram
U.S. Statehood Quarters
Colorized24K Gold PlatedHologram
American Silver Eagles
Star Notes
Coin Capsules/Supplies
Felt Coin BoxesCoin CapsulesCoin StandsMisc Supplies
BOGO (Buy One, Get One Free)
SOLD OUT
BLACK RUTHENIUM COINS
CHINESE LUCKY MONEY
Donald Trump *45th President*
Home
About Us
FAQ
Customer Service
Large Size Bills
Lucky Money Federal Reserve Banknotes (Red Folders)
Other Lucky Money Themed Bills
CNY Envelopes
Colorized Coins
JFK Kennedy Half Dollars
Art
Astrology/Horoscopes
Animals
Entertainment
Sports
Football (NFL)
Baseball
Hockey (NHL)
Nascar
Entertainment
Commemorative Coins
Colorized Currency
Entertainment
Enhanced Bills (all denominations)
Sports
Political
$2 Parks/States
$2 Statehood
$1 States
World/Historical Events
Misc Bills
Hologram Currency
Misc Supplies
BOGO (Buy One, Get One Free)
SOLD OUT
BLACK RUTHENIUM COINS
CHINESE LUCKY MONEY
Donald Trump *45th President*
Home
/
Privacy Policy - The Merrick Mint, Ltd.
Privacy Policy
Privacy & Security
All the information regarding our privacy policy can be found on this page that you are currently reading and more info about the privacy policy cookies can be found here.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.  When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
- To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
- To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.  We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. To find more about our cookies policy, please visit our cookies policy page. To check if your browser has cookies enabled or you need information about enabling cookies, you can visit this page.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  As part of the Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Special Deal
Black Ruthenium JFK 2015-P
Expires in:
Latest products
2020 YEAR OF THE RAT $1 & $2 Chinese New Year Lucky Money Set - DUAL 8’s GOLD MATCHING RAT’s in Premium RED LUNAR ENVELOPE – Limited & Numbered of 8,888 Sets Worldwide
$39.95
2021 YEAR OF THE OX $1 & $2 Chinese New Year Lucky Money Set - DUAL 8’s GOLD MATCHING OXEN in Premium RED LUNAR ENVELOPE – Limited & Numbered of 8,888 Sets Worldwide
$39.95
Add to Cart
ALL 43 United States PRESIDENTS 43-Coin Complete Set Colorized State US Quarters
$339.95
See All
